<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Milan Zerbin</title>
    <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Milan Zerbin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 09:30:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workshop: AImath</title>
      <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/workshop-aimath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/workshop-aimath/</guid>
      <description>AI Transforms Math Research During the week 25-28 August 2025, Kai Cieliebak and i will host a workshop on the use of AI tools in mathematical research in Augsburg, Germany.&#xA;You can check out more details on the workshop website.&#xA;Feel free to join!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C.I.M.E Summerschool</title>
      <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/cime-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/cime-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Symplectic Dynamics and Topology During the week 16-20 of June 2025, i had the pleasure to attend a wonderful summerschool in the pittoresque Gran Hotel San Michele in Calabria, Italy.&#xA;Next to meeting loads of inspiring young researchers of the symplectic world and beyond, no matter my limited understanding i had a great time listening to the four lecture series held there:&#xA;Marie-Claude Arnaud: Conformal symplectic dynamics Viktor Ginzburg: Symplectic dynamics Michael Hutchings: Low dimensional symplectic dynamics Claude Viterbo: Completion of the set of Lagrangians and applications to dynamics At your own risk: Clicking on any of the lecture series guides you to the download of my hardly readable chaotic handwritten notes from their talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockseminar</title>
      <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar25/</guid>
      <description>Ricci Flow and the sphere-theorem During the week 10-14 of June 2025, i attended for the fourth time now the annual Augsburg-Potsdam joint &amp;ldquo;Blockseminar&amp;rdquo;, this year lodging in Hotel Bollmannsruh at Beetzsee, Brandenburg.&#xA;This years goal was to learn the technique of ricci flow, guided by the book of S. Brendle. You can find the schedule of the Seminar here.&#xA;Organization The seminar was organized by Christian Bär and Bernhard Hanke with help from Lennard Ronge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterthesis</title>
      <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/masterthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/masterthesis/</guid>
      <description>My masterthesis was on the topic &amp;ldquo;spaces of positive curvature metrics on nonorientable manifolds&amp;rdquo;. You can find a pdf version here and the entire LaTeX-Code in the Git-Repository.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockseminar</title>
      <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar24/</guid>
      <description>Scalar curvature: Rigidity and Flexibility During the week 28. of April to 03. of May 2024, i attended for the third time the annual Augsburg-Potsdam joint &amp;ldquo;Blockseminar&amp;rdquo;, this year lodging in Kloster Banz at Beetzsee, Brandenburg.&#xA;This years goal was to learn about flexibility and rigidity phenomenons of scalar curvature. You can find the schedule of the Seminar here.&#xA;Organization The seminar was organized by Christian Bär and Bernhard Hanke with help from Georg Frenck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockseminar</title>
      <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar23/</guid>
      <description>The Nash&amp;ndash;Moser Inverse Function Theorem During the week 18-25 of June 2023, i attended for the already second time the annual Augsburg-Potsdam joint &amp;ldquo;Blockseminar&amp;rdquo;, this year lodging in Hotel Bollmannsruh at Beetzsee, Brandenburg.&#xA;This years goal was to learn all about Frechet spaces and the proof of the inverse function theorem of Nash and Moser. We stuck close to Hamiltons excellent and freely accesible book on the topic. You can find the schedule of the Seminar here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockseminar</title>
      <link>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://milanzerbin.github.io/activities/blockseminar22/</guid>
      <description>H-principles and Convex Integration During the first week in may 2022, i attended for my first time the annual Augsburg-Potsdam joint &amp;ldquo;Blockseminar&amp;rdquo;, that year lodging in Kloster Frauenwörth on the Chiemsee in Bavaria.&#xA;We spent the week learning about convex integration, proving the h-principle for open and ample relations and discussing applications. You can find the schedule of the seminar here.&#xA;Organization The seminar was organized by Christian Bär and Bernhard Hanke with help from Artem Nepechy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
